https://www.tbirdslotracing.com.au/privacy-policy/

Ph: (08) 8262 2262 |
91 Research Road, Pooraka, South Australia |
Free shipping over $100 (excludes sets)
Menu
Search
My Account
Thunderbird Slot Racing logo
Search:
Search
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.My AccountMy WishlistLog In
Menu
HomeSlot Cars 1/32 Scale Slot Cars1/24 Scale Slot Cars1/43 Scale Slot CarsSlot Car KitsSpecial EditionsComing SoonRacing Sets and Track Racing SetsDigitalTrack Extension PiecesTrack AccessoriesHand ControllersTrack BordersBarriersLap CountersPower SuppliesSpares & Performance MotorsChassisGearsBearings and BushingsAxlesAxle KitsWheelsTyresMagnetsCar BodiesDecals and Paint MasksHand Controller PartsOther spare partsAccessories Slot Car ToolsFluids & LubricationCataloguesOther AccessoriesPaintSale Items
Home
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis following document sets forth the Privacy Policy for the Thunderbird Slot Racing website, www.tbirdslotracing.com.au.Thunderbird Slot Racing is committed to providing you with the best possible customer service experience. Thunderbird Slot Racing is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Crh), which sets out a number of principles concerning the privacy of individuals.Collection of your personal informationThere are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, for access to future Thunderbird Slot Racing customer support features you are required to submit personally identifiable information. This may include but not limited to a unique username and password, or provide sensitive information in the recovery of your lost password.Sharing of your personal informationWe may occasionally hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or customer freight shipping. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. Thunderbird Slot Racing takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.Use of your personal informationFor each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.Changes to this Privacy PolicyThunderbird Slot Racing reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.Accessing Your Personal InformationYou have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons. Thunderbird Slot Racing reserves the right to charge a fee for searching for, and providing access to, your information on a per request basis. Contacting usThunderbird Slot Racing welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us by any of the following means:Call: (08) 8262 2262Post: Attn: Privacy PolicyThunderbird Slot RacingUnit 6, 91 Research RoadPooraka SA 5095AustraliaE-mail: info@tbirdslotracing.com.auConnectContact us FacebookCustomer serviceMy accountShipping information and returnsPrivacy policyTerms of serviceSecurityInformationAbout usOur shop and racewayBirthday parties, events and track hireVIP MembershipShop & Raceway Opening HoursMondayClosedTuesdayClosedWednesday1pm - 9pmThursday1pm - 4pmFriday1pm - 9:30pmSaturday10am - 5pmSundayClosed Public HolidaysClosedSchool holidaysSee here
Newsletter
Subscribe
© 2018 Thunderbird Slot Racing. All Rights Reserved.
